<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<schemalist gettext-domain="vocal">
	<schema id="com.github.VocalPodcastProject.vocal" path="/com/github/VocalPodcastProject/vocal/">
	    <key name="auto-download" type="b">
			<default>true</default>
			<summary>Whether or not Vocal should automatically download new episodes</summary>
			<description>
				Whether or not Vocal should automatically download new episodes when they are available.
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="autoclean-library" type="b">
			<default>true</default>
			<summary>Whether or not Vocal should automatically delete old downloaded episdes</summary>
			<description>
				Whether or not Vocal should automatically delete downloaded, played episodes that are more
				than a week old.
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="window-width" type="i">
			<default>750</default>
			<summary>The user's last window width</summary>
			<description>
				The user's last window width
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="window-height" type="i">
			<default>450</default>
			<summary>The user's last window height</summary>
			<description>
				The user's last window height
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="update-interval" type="i">
			<default>30</default>
			<summary>The number of minutes between checking for episodes</summary>
			<description>
				The number of minutes to wait between checking for new episodes
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="fast-forward-seconds" type="i">
			<default>30</default>
			<summary>The number of seconds to fast forward</summary>
			<description>
				The number of seconds to fast forward
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="rewind-seconds" type="i">
			<default>30</default>
			<summary>The number of seconds to rewind</summary>
			<description>
				The number of seconds to rewind
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="last-played-media" type="s">
			<default>""</default>
			<summary>The podcast and episode that was last playing</summary>
			<description>
				The podcast and episode that was last played, in podcast_name,episode_title format
			</description>
		</key>

	  <key name="last-queue-contents" type="s">
			<default>""</default>
			<summary>The episodes left in the queue when Vocal was last closed</summary>
			<description>
				The episodes left in the queue when Vocal was last closed, in
			  podcast_name, episide_title format, separated by semicolons
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="continue-running-after-close" type="b">
			<default>true</default>
			<summary>Whether or not Vocal should run in the background after closing</summary>
			<description>
				Whether or not Vocal should keep running in the background for feed updates and downloads.
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="itunes-store-country" type="s">
			<default>"us"</default>
			<summary>The iTunes country code to search for results</summary>
			<description>
				When finding the top n podcasts, Vocal will search for results from a particular country's iTunes Store.
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="show-name-label" type="b">
			<default>false</default>
			<summary>Whether or not Vocal should display the names of podcasts in the local library</summary>
			<description>
				When enabled, Vocal will show an extra label beneath the cover art in the library with the name of the podcast.
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="dark-mode-enabled" type="b">
			<default>false</default>
			<summary>Whether or not Vocal should use the dark theme instead of the light theme.</summary>
			<description>
				When enabled, Vocal will use the dark version of the GTK theme and modify the headerbar color if on elementary OS.
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="theme-preference" type="s">
			<default>"system"</default>
			<summary>Which theme to use</summary>
			<description>
				Whether to use 'system', 'light', or 'dark' theme.
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="newest-episodes-first" type="b">
			<default>true</default>
			<summary>Whether to show the newest episodes highest up in the list, or at the bottom</summary>
			<description>
				When set to true, Vocal will show the newest episodes at the top of episode lists. When false, the oldest
				will be at the top.
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="keep-playing-in-background" type="b">
			<default>true</default>
			<summary>Whether or not to keep Vocal playing in the background</summary>
			<description>
				When set to true, Vocal will keep running and playing in the background when the
				close button is pressed. When set to false, Vocal will exit the program when
				close is pressed.
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="gpodder-device-name" type="s">
			<default>"vocal"</default>
			<summary>The name of the device for gpodder.net</summary>
			<description>
				The name of the device that gets displayed on gpodder.net. Typically,
				it is set to some combination of "vocal" and the hardware device name.
				That said, you can get as creative as you want.
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="gpodder-username" type="s">
			<default>""</default>
			<summary>The username of the last successfully logged-in gpodder.net user</summary>
			<description>
				Contains the username of the last gpodder.net user account to successfully
				login to the service.
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="gpodder-sync-episode-status" type="b">
			<default>true</default>
			<summary>Whether or not to keep episode status in sync with the cloud</summary>
			<description>
				When set to true, Vocal will automatically sync all the episode statuses with
				gpodder.net, including whether or not an episode has been listened to, as well as
				playback progress.
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="gpodder-remove-deleted-podcasts" type="b">
			<default>false</default>
			<summary>Whether or not to remove podcasts that are no longer in the gpodder.net subscriptions</summary>
			<description>
				When set to true, Vocal will automatically remove a podcast from the library when
				it is no longer in the user's gpodder.net subscription list (typically following
				a delete event from another device).
			</description>
		</key>

		<key name="gpodder-last-successful-sync-timestamp" type="s">
			<default>""</default>
			<summary>The UNIX timestamp of the last successful episode sync</summary>
			<description>
				The UNIX timestamp of the last time Vocal successfully contacted the
				gpodder.net service and received an update of episode actions.
			</description>
		</key>
	</schema>
</schemalist>

